let savollar18 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "armor",
      answer: "C. sovut",
      options: [
        "A. dubulg'a",
        "B. qalqon",
        "C. sovut",
        "D. zirah"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "to blaze",
      answer: "A. yonmoq",
      options: [
        "A. yonmoq",
        "B. tutamoq",
        "C. alangalanmoq",
        "D. cho'g'lanmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "to boom",
      answer: "D. bang'illamoq",
      options: [
        "A. qarsillamoq",
        "B. portlamoq",
        "C. yangramoq",
        "D. bang'illamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "cliff",
      answer: "B. tik qoya",
      options: [
        "A. qoya",
        "B. tik qoya",
        "C. tepalik",
        "D. tog'"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "flame",
      answer: "C. alanga",
      options: [
        "A. olov",
        "B. cho'g'",
        "C. alanga",
        "D. tutun"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "independence",
      answer: "A. mustaqillik",
      options: [
        "A. mustaqillik",
        "B. hokimiyat",
        "C. hukmronlik",
        "D. boshqaruv"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "invasion",
      answer: "D. bosqin",
      options: [
        "A. hujum",
        "B. urush",
        "C. kurash",
        "D. bosqin"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "knight",
      answer: "B. ritsar",
      options: [
        "A. askar",
        "B. ritsar",
        "C. jangchi",
        "D. pahlavon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "lightning",
      answer: "C. chaqmoq",
      options: [
        "A. momaqaldiroq",
        "B. bo'ron",
        "C. chaqmoq",
        "D. yashin"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "rebel",
      answer: "A. isyonchi",
      options: [
        "A. isyonchi",
        "B. xoin",
        "C. dushman",
        "D. raqib"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "to retreat",
      answer: "D. chekinmoq",
      options: [
        "A. qochmoq",
        "B. ketmoq",
        "C. yugurmoq",
        "D. chekinmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "revolution",
      answer: "B. inqilob",
      options: [
        "A. isyon",
        "B. inqilob",
        "C. qo'zg'olon",
        "D. to'ntarish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "spear",
      answer: "C. nayza",
      options: [
        "A. qilich",
        "B. xanjar",
        "C. nayza",
        "D. bolta"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "steep",
      answer: "A. tik",
      options: [
        "A. tik",
        "B. baland",
        "C. qiya",
        "D. chuqur"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "summit",
      answer: "D. cho'qqi",
      options: [
        "A. yuqori",
        "B. balandlik",
        "C. tog'",
        "D. cho'qqi"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "thunder",
      answer: "B. momaqaldiroq",
      options: [
        "A. shovqin",
        "B. momaqaldiroq",
        "C. gumbur",
        "D. ovoz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "troops",
      answer: "C. qo'shin",
      options: [
        "A. armiya",
        "B. lashkar",
        "C. qo'shin",
        "D. harbiylar"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "warrior",
      answer: "A. jangchi",
      options: [
        "A. jangchi",
        "B. askar",
        "C. sipoh",
        "D. qahramon"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to withdraw",
      answer: "D. chekinmoq",
      options: [
        "A. ketmoq",
        "B. qochmoq",
        "C. chiqmoq",
        "D. chekinmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "to yield",
      answer: "B. taslim bo'lmoq",
      options: [
        "A. olmoq",
        "B. taslim bo'lmoq",
        "C. egilmoq",
        "D. bermoq"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar18;